Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 3: Boxes 45-66
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 3: Boxes 45-66
- Box: 58, Folder: 4 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 61: Relations Reviews, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. December 7, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 62: Relations Reviews, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. December 21, 1970. Item is in English.
  - Item 63: Relations Reviews, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. January 11. Item is in English.
  - Item 64: Relations Reviews, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. January 25. Item is in English.
  - Item 65: Relations Reviews, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. February 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 66: Relations Reviews, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. February 22. Item is in English.
  - Item 67: Relations Reviews, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. March 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 68: Relations Reviews, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. March 22. Item is in English.
  - Item 69: Relations Reviews, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. March 29. Item is in English.
  - Item 70: Relations Reviews, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. April 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 71: Relations Reviews, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. April 19. Item is in English.
  - Item 72: Relations Reviews, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. April 26. Item is in English.
  - Item 73: Relations Reviews, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. May 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 74: The Construction Roundtable: Progress and the Outlook Ahead, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. November 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 75: Productivity, Wages and the Profit Picture, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
    By Frank E. Highton. Item is in English.
  - Item 76: General Electric's Commitment to Progress in Equal Opportunity and Minority Relations, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 77: Marketing And Public Affairs, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 78: Marketing And Public Relations Services, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 79: General Electric Industrial Relations Materials, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 80: Productivity, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 81: "he Quest For Leadership And Excellence, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 82: Labor Policy, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 83: Labor Management Relations in a Newly Competitive World, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 84: Labor-Management Relations and Economic Growth: The Role of Industry, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 85: "Business and the Urban Crisis", Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 86: Report to the General Electric Share Owners, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 87: Taxes And Economic Growth, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 88: America Discovers The New World:, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 89: Energizing Economic Growth, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 90: Energizing Economic Growth, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 91: Our Common Cause in World Competition, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 92: The Creative Power of Profits, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 93: The Creative Power of Profits, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 94: Reflections of an American, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 95: Crisis of the Cities: A Corporate Concern, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 96: Management Education: A Career-Long Process, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 97: Should Pay Be Equal Everywhere?, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 98: Basic Rights On Trial?, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 99: Take a New Look at Performance Appraisal, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 100: Bulletin, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Item 101: Bulletin, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. September 17. Item is in English.
  - Item 102: Bulletin, Publication (Box 58, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. November 13. Item is in English.
- Box: 58, Folder: 5 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Service with the Federal Government by GE Employees, Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. Community and Government Relations Bulletin; Nov 13th, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: General Electric's 1963 Negotiations; What About "Intervention"?, Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: A Report to Management: Complusory Unionism, Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Another Look at the "Wage Guideposts", Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. April 13, 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: A New Opportunity for Brand Names, Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
    By L. R. Boulware. March 30, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: News Release; 3/31/1948, Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
    By G. H. Pfeif. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: News Release; 4/1/1948, Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: News Release; 5/26/1948, Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: What about Pay Increases which Starve Recovery and Feed Inflation?, Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
    5/19/1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Search for Leadership, Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
    By Richard J. Anton. 5/5/1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: GE Industrial Relations Materials April - June 1966, Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: A Letter to Sales and Service People on the Outlook for 1966 Negotiations, Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
    7/12/1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Pension Plan, Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
    9/30/1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Savings and Stock Bonus Plan, Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
    2/21/1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: GE's Philosophy and Approach for Manager Development, Publication (Box 58, Folder 5)
    By Harold F. Smiddy. Item is in English.
- Box: 58, Folder: 6 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Management Conferences on Human Relations, Publication (Box 58, Folder 6)
    (An entire volume, it should be in a three ring binder). Item is in English.
- Box: 59, Folder: 1 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Western Europe/ USA Technical Education Systems: A Comparison, Publication (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Growth and Managerial Planning, Publication (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: The Shorter Work Week and Its Implications, Publication (Box 59, Folder 1)
    By Joseph M. Bertotti. 2/17/1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Labor-Management Relations and Economic Growth: The Role of Industry, Publication (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Adventures In Jet Power, Publication (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Inside the Atom, Publication (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Adventures in Electronics, Publication (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Engineering in your future, Publication (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Land of Plenty, Publication (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Land of Plenty: A Story of Freedom and Power, Publication (Box 59, Folder 1)
    c.2. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Electricity Around Us, Publication (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Science in your Future, Publication (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Man-Made Magic, Publication (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: The Story of The Turbine, Publication (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: The Nature Of The Work Of The Chief Executive, Publication (Box 59, Folder 1)
    September 16, 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Power For Progress In The Air, Publication (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: A report to management: Compulsory Unionism, Publication (Box 59, Folder 1)
    By Philip D. Moore. April 5, 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Tables for Costing Compensation Increases: Labor Economics Research, Publication (Box 59, Folder 1)
    January 29, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The General Electric ForumL A Journal of Leadership Opinion, Publication (Box 59, Folder 1)
    Volume X No. 4 Winter 1967-68. Item is in English.
- Box: 59, Folder: 2 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Letter the the Honorable Andrew Jacobs, Publication (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Emergency and Plan, Publication (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Letter from Charles E. Wilson President, General Electric Company to the Honorable Andrew Jacobs Member, House Committee on Education and Labor, Publication (Box 59, Folder 2)
    By Charles E. Wilson. March 10, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: General Electric, Publication (Box 59, Folder 2)
    Emergency Aid Plan. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: 1957 Year-End Review of Freedom's Old But New Problem of Better Defense Or Better Living Or Both!, Publication (Box 59, Folder 2)
    Dece,ber 31, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Picture-Story Feature, Publication (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Management: GE Tailors a Plant Project, Publication (Box 59, Folder 2)
    November 7, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Automation in General Electric: The Human Side of the Story, Publication (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Perspectives in an Age of Protest: Address to The Rocky Mountain College Placement Officers Las Vegas, Nevada, Publication (Box 59, Folder 2)
    October 2, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Commitment to Individual Responsibility: At the Commencement Exercises Southeastern Massachusetts Technological Institute, Publication (Box 59, Folder 2)
    June 9, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Is Today's Labor-Management Relations Relevant?, Publication (Box 59, Folder 2)
    By Virgil B. Day. October 3, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: For Immediate Release, Publication (Box 59, Folder 2)
    By N. Herington. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Business Operations In Our Changing Environment, Publication (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: Release to morning papers of March 24, 1948, Publication (Box 59, Folder 2)
    March 23, 948. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Tjos fp;;pwomg os a [ress re;ease frp, the General Electric co., Publication (Box 59, Folder 2)
    March 2, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The following is a press release from the General Electric co., Publication (Box 59, Folder 2)
    By L. R. Boulware. March 3, 1948. Item is in English.
- Box: 59, Folder: 3 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Automation, Employment, and Unemployment, Publication (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Employment and Unemployment: In the U.S. Economy, In General Electric, Publication (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Programs for Progress: We Unite for a Greater Measure of Justice, Publication (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: The Creative Power of Profits, Publication (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: The Rising Wealth of General Electric and The Declining Living Standards of its Employees, Publication (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: The General Electric Forum Vol XII(1) Spring 1969, Publication (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: The General Electric Forum Vol IX (2) April-June 1966, Publication (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: The General Electric Forum Vol X (3) Autumn 1967, Publication (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: The General Electric Forum Vol X (2) April-June 1967, Publication (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: The General Electric Forum Vol X (1) Jan-March 1967, Publication (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: The General Electric Forum Vol IX (4) Oct-Dec 1966, Publication (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: The General Electric Forum Vol IX (3) July-September 1966, Publication (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: The Rising Wealth of General Electric and the Declining Standard of Living of its Employees, Publication (Box 59, Folder 3)
    By Union of GE Employees. Criticizes GE wages. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: GE Reports 11% Rise in Profits 10/9/69, Publication (Box 59, Folder 3)
    By Gene Smith. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: GE Profit Rose 11% in 3rd Quarter and Nine Months, Publication (Box 59, Folder 3)
    By Wall Street Journal. 10/9/1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Analysis of GE's Inferior Offer on Wages, Benefits, and Contract Provisions, Publication (Box 59, Folder 3)
    By United Electrical Radio and Machine Workers of America 10/13/69. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The 1969 Colective Bargaining Demands on GE Confernece Board 5/22-23/1969, Publication (Box 59, Folder 3)
    By United Electrical Radio and Machine Workers of America. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Graphs Reguarding the Need for Wage Increases form GE 10/24/69, Publication (Box 59, Folder 3)
    By International Brotherhood of Teamsters. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Proposal by IUE for 1969-1970 negotiations, Publication (Box 59, Folder 3)
    By Intenration Union of Electrical Workers. Item is in English.
- Box: 59, Folder: 4 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: General Electric Schenectady News, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. September 23, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Charles Edward Wilson: American Industrialist, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By Kent Sagendorph. September 2, 1914. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: 2 New Year's Resolutions, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. January 5, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: What About Housing?, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. November 14, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: What About Housing?, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. November 14, 1947; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Who Told You these Fairy Tales?, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. December 5, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Who Told You these Fairy Tales?, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. December 5, 1947; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Should Pay be Equal Everywhere?, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. December 12, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Should Pay be Equal Everywhere?, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. December 12, 1947; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Should Wages Go Up -- and Down -- with Profits?, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. December 19, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Should Wages Go Up -- and Down -- with Profits?, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. December 19, 1947; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Should Wages Go Up -- and Down -- with Profits?, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. December 19, 1947; Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: General Electric Cuts Prices!, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. January 9, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: General Electric Cuts Prices!, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. January 9, 1948; Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: General Electric Cuts Prices!, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. January 9, 1948; Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Good Way, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: Why Must We Save More -- as Well as Produce More?, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. January 23, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Are Prices Coming Down?, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. February 6, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: What's Helping You Conquer Inflation?, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. February 13, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: What Do You Think?, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. February 27, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Thrift is Needed to Curb Inflation, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. March 5, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: If There Were a 3rd Round, the Referee Might Get Knocked Out, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. March 12, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Let's See How We All Made Out, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. March 19 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: How Does General Electric Feel About Unions?, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. April 2, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Report to Employees on Negotiations, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. April 30, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Our Replies to Some Questions About: Check-Off, Union Membership, Strike, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. May 21, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Who Is Telling the Truth -- And Who Isn't?, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. May 28, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Text of General Electric's Wage Offer to UE-CIO, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. June 11, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: What Did General Electric Learn?, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. July 30, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Why Are You Paying High Prices?, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. August 6, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Whose Promises Were Kept?, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. August 13, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: How Can We All Live Better?, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. September 17, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: A Plague on Both Your Houses, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. September 24, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: G.E. Reports a Profit -- and Progress for All, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. October 22, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Let Us Give Thanks, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. November 19, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: What is the Trouble?, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Item 37: How Would You Revise Our Labor Laws?, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. January 21, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: How Did We All Make Out in '48?, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. March 11, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Where the Money Goes, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. April 22, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Jobs Depend on Faith, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. May 6, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 41: What About Job Security?, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. May 20, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 42: What is a Speed-Up?, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. May 27, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 43: Is Mama in a "Speed-Up" Too?, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. June 3, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 44: On "Being Ourselves", Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. July 1, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 45: "I Don't Want to Be Agitated", Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Item 46: Why We Oppose a 4th Round, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. July 20 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 47: Who Wants Profits? Who Gets Them?, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. July 29, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 48: High Wages -- Low prices? We Can Have Them!, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. September 16, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 49: New Meeting Arranged, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. September 30, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 50: The "Anxious Bench", Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. October 7, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 51: We Must Be Neutral, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. November 18, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 52: In the Middle, Publication (Box 59, Folder 4)
    By General Electric. December 9, 1949. Item is in English.
- Box: 59, Folder: 5 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Aid to Education 1969, Publication (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Corporate Alumnus Program 1969, Publication (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Our Future Business Environment: A Re-Evaluation, Publication (Box 59, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. July, 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Monogram, Publication (Box 59, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. November-December 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Relations Reviews, Publication (Box 59, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. May 1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Community and Government Relations Bulletin: For Circulation Among General Electric Managers, Publication (Box 59, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. September 17, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Truth In Bargaining and Free Speech: A General Electric View, Publication (Box 59, Folder 5)
    By Virgil B. Day. February 4, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Report to the General Electric Share Owners, Publication (Box 59, Folder 5)
    By Fred J. Borch. April 26, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: General Electric Foundation Annual Report: 1966, Publication (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Crisis of the Cities: A Corporate Concern, Publication (Box 59, Folder 5)
    By Gerald L. Phillippe. May 1, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Monogram, Publication (Box 59, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. May 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Monogram, Publication (Box 59, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. August 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Monogram, Publication (Box 59, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. October 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Monogram, Publication (Box 59, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. November 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: The Monogram, Publication (Box 59, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. December-January 1968-1969. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Monogram, Publication (Box 59, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. June-July 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Crisis of the Cities: A Corporate Concern, Publication (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Item 18: Employee Relations News, Publication (Box 59, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. January 29, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Employee Relations News, Publication (Box 59, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. January 22, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Employee Relations News, Publication (Box 59, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. January 15, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Employee Relations News, Publication (Box 59, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. March 4, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Employee Relations News, Publication (Box 59, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. February 19, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Employee Relations News, Publication (Box 59, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. March 11, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Employee Relations News, Publication (Box 59, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. March 18, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Employee Relations News, Publication (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Item 26: Employee Relations News, Publication (Box 59, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. March 25, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Employee Relations News, Publication (Box 59, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. April 1, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Employee Relations News, Publication (Box 59, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. April 10, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Employee Relations News, Publication (Box 59, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. November 20, 1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Employee Relations News, Publication (Box 59, Folder 5)
    By General Electric. November 6, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Avoiding a 'Productivity Crisis', Publication (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Item 32: General Electric Industrial Relations Materials, Publication (Box 59, Folder 5)